Brett Tindall

Greater Toronto Area, Canada



brett.tindall@dcmail.ca



linkedin.com/in/brett-tindall

Summary

My name is Brett Tindall and I am a very passionate and dedicated programmer.

That may be the most cliche introduction sentence ever written but for me its nothing but the truth. My dream is to one day create my own video game, hopefully a fully fledged MMORPG title, and I work hard everyday to make sure one day, if I'm lucky enough to get the opportunity, I'm ready to bring my dream to life. That is why I am currently going to school for Computer Programming at Durham College but on top of that I often find myself working on my own passion projects, such as a wpf that counts wins and losses in a fighting game and calculates the odds of entered match ups and a simple console game that allows you to grow and evolve your own monster with it gaining different traits as it grows depending on how you treat it (this one if going to be a WIP for a while but I still enjoy working on it when I get the time).

I have some basic experience working on hardware and software for friends and family but most of my job experience comes from years in retail and fast food. I have been working part time in these industries ever since I was 15, which may not have provided my with any computer experience but it gave me ample amounts of customer service experience. On top of my work experience I have also been a part of many teams, anything from sports to video games, and have also found myself being elected by the teams to act as their captain. This is because I am always looking at the big picture and can use this to inspire proper teamwork by letting each teammate know their value and how they stand in the grand plan, which usually goes better than telling everybody what to do with no explanation.

On top of making video games I also enjoy playing them, as was previously mentioned, and tend to spend most of my free time either doing that or hanging out with friends. I am currently playing a lot of osrs and RS6 in hopes of hitting the new champion rank.

Experience



Staff Member

Mr. Sub
Jul 2019 - Present (1 year 8 months +)



Staff Member

The Perfect Scoop Jun 2017 - Feb 2019 (1 year 9 months)

Tun Hortons Staff Member

Tim Hortons
Jul 2015 - May 2017 (1 year 11 months)

Education

DC Durham College

Associate's degree, Computer Programming 2018 - 2020

Port Perry High School

High School Diploma 2014 - 2018

S.A. Cawker Public School

2006 - 2014

Skills

Customer Service • Teamwork • C++ • Sports • Visual Basic .NET (VB.NET) • C# • SQL • Team Leadership